<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jayden Bayangos-Brandt</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Jayden Bayangos-Brandt</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jbayangosb.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jbayangosb.github.io/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>My name is Jayden Bayangos-Brandt, I&amp;rsquo;m from Melbourne, Australia, and live in the faraway suburb of Cranbourne with my beautiful wife. I have a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Information Technology from &lt;a href="https://www.rmit.edu.au/" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">RMIT&lt;/a>. I have been working as an Android Software Engineer for the past 7 years. I have worked on a variety of projects, from small startups to large corporations. I have experience working in various areas of Android development, ranging from Jetpack Compose to Room, PDFs and troublesome 3rd Party SDKs. Always keen to approach a problem with curiosity.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Train Flux Lora</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/posts/train-flux-lora/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jbayangosb.github.io/posts/train-flux-lora/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="how-to-train-a-flux-lora-to-make-pictures-of-you">
 How to train a Flux LORA to make pictures of you!
 &lt;a class="heading-link" href="#how-to-train-a-flux-lora-to-make-pictures-of-you">
 &lt;i class="fa-solid fa-link" aria-hidden="true" title="Link to heading">&lt;/i>
 &lt;span class="sr-only">Link to heading&lt;/span>
 &lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>I had a lot of difficulty trying to figure out how to train a LORA for flux on my system.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(4070 with 12GB VRAM)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So after a bunch of trial and error I compiled this mini tutorial with as much guidance as I needed.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hopefully this can help someone else out in the future!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ANZ Plus</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/anz-plus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/anz-plus/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of &lt;a href="https://ittybittyapps.com" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Itty Bitty Apps&lt;/a>, I was the first Android Engineer to work on this greenfield project. Not often you get an opportunity to click &amp;ldquo;Create Project&amp;rdquo; in Android Studio. I was deeply involved with many significant aspects of the app, from establishing the architecture, developing the authentication flows, and pioneering roles in the project such as Domain Enablement.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My time here took me to different parts of the app starting in Transactions, Registration and Onboarding, Open Banking and finally involved in the Home Loan journey. The team may have been the largest Native Mobile team I have ever been a part of with a peak count of over 150 iOS and Android Engineers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>AGL Energy</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/agl-energy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/agl-energy/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of &lt;a href="https://ittybittyapps.com" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Itty Bitty Apps&lt;/a>, I joined the project at a late stage in the development cycle. The app aimed to replace it&amp;rsquo;s previous Xamarin iteration with a fully native experience. As a Junior Engineer I took over from a Senior Engineer with 6 months until the release date and quickly made an impact under deadline pressure, helping to secure a successful release.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can find the app on the &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=agl.digital.mobile&amp;amp;hl=en_AU" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Google Play Store.&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Coles</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/coles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/coles/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of &lt;a href="https://ittybittyapps.com" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Itty Bitty Apps&lt;/a> and as a Junior Engineer, I joined the team out at Coles to help with the Android app. This was the first engagment between my consulting company and Coles. and as a Junior Engineer at the time, I was excited to be a part of it. The app was already in a mature state, but I was able to contribute to the project successfully and helped secure a lasting partnership with Coles remaining a client of Itty Bitty Apps for 7+ years.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fastmail</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/fastmail/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/fastmail/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of &lt;a href="https://ittybittyapps.com" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Itty Bitty Apps&lt;/a>, I conducted an audit of the Fastmail project. I identified and provided recommendations for a variety of technical tasks with the aim of uplifting the project to meet modern Android standards. After producing this report, I was engaged to implement the recommendations. This involved a complete rewrite of the app to use modern Android architecture components and best practices.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After that successful rewrite, I went on to be involved with even more substantial enhancements to the project, going beyond uplifting to build brand new features such as e2e encrypted notifications and in-app PDF viewing.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>AIA Vitality</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/aia-vitality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/aia-vitality/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of &lt;a href="https://ittybittyapps.com" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Itty Bitty Apps&lt;/a>, I joined the team at AIA Vitality with an aim to help uplift the aging Java codebase to Kotlin as the new Google endorsed language of choice. This was a large project and required an incremental approach as feature delivery was still an ongoing requirement. By the end of my time on the project 90% of the codebase was converted to Kotlin as I mentored a Junior Engineer to take over my role as Lead Android Engineer.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Supp</title><link>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/supp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jbayangosb.github.io/projects/supp/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of &lt;a href="https://ittybittyapps.com" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Itty Bitty Apps&lt;/a>, I kickstarted the Android project as a solo developer. As this was earlier in my career, I focussed on porting the logic from the iOS app with a view to achieve parity. I was able to build a login experience that interacted with the backend before I was moved to another project.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Later in my time with &lt;a href="https://ittybittyapps.com" class="external-link" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Itty Bitty Apps&lt;/a>, I returned to the project with it now it a much more mature state and addressed numerous issues affecting the peformance of the app.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>